[
  {
    "front": ".hide()",
    "back": "Hide the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": ".show()",
    "back": "Display the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": ".toggle()",
    "back": "Display or hide the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": ".animate()",
    "back": "Perform a custom animation of a set of CSS properties."
  },
  {
    "front": ".clearQueue()",
    "back": "Remove from the queue all items that have not yet been run."
  },
  {
    "front": ".delay()",
    "back": "Set a timer to delay execution of subsequent items in the queue."
  },
  {
    "front": ".dequeue()",
    "back": "Execute the next function on the queue for the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.dequeue()",
    "back": "Execute the next function on the queue for the matched element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".finish()",
    "back": "Stop the currently-running animation, remove all queued animations, and complete all animations for the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.fx.interval",
    "back": "The rate (in milliseconds) at which animations fire."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.fx.off",
    "back": "Globally disable all animations."
  },
  {
    "front": ".queue()",
    "back": "Show or manipulate the queue of functions to be executed on the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery.queue()",
    "back": "Show or manipulate the queue of functions to be executed on the matched element."
  },
  {
    "front": ".stop()",
    "back": "Stop the currently-running animation on the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": ".fadeIn()",
    "back": "Display the matched elements by fading them to opaque."
  },
  {
    "front": ".fadeOut()",
    "back": "Hide the matched elements by fading them to transparent."
  },
  {
    "front": ".fadeTo()",
    "back": "Adjust the opacity of the matched elements."
  },
  {
    "front": ".fadeToggle()",
    "back": "Display or hide the matched elements by animating their opacity."
  },
  {
    "front": ".slideDown()",
    "back": "Display the matched elements with a sliding motion."
  },
  {
    "front": ".slideToggle()",
    "back": "Display or hide the matched elements with a sliding motion."
  },
  {
    "front": ".slideUp()",
    "back": "Hide the matched elements with a sliding motion."
  }
]
